

KELLY OO KAI LI BARCHELOR OF BUSINESS (HONS) IN MANAGEMENT

■ kellyookaili97@gmail.com | ↑ 18-7-6, Jalan Tun Dr Awang, 11900 Bayan Lepas, Pulau Pinang. | ↓ (60)16-4031763 |

### **ABOUT ME**

An outgoing, proactive and ambitious individual who is motivated by opportunity for advancement to levels of responsibility where I can use my skills as a team builder, motivator and mover. Strongly focused on cohesion, communication, morale and team accomplishments to achieve goals through and with the team. Have the experienced in managing and marketing career, ability to come up with interesting ideas for unforgettable marketing campaigns and follow instructions and deliver quality results. Thus, I am Extremely motivated to constantly develop my skills and grow professionally.

### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

### Teadaye Malaysia

Penang, MY

Marketing Executive

Oct. 2019 - Current

- Focused on Internal & External Marketing.
- Create awareness, conduct facebook campaign, manage social media
- Deal with 3rd party (Hunza group, Capitalist, Delivery platform, etc)
- Conduct Grand opening for Gurney Paragon & Gurney Plaza Teadaye.
- Photoshooting (drinks,influencer), arrange influencer for adsvertiseent, collaboration

#### Malaysia Kangtao

Penang, MY

Mar. 2019 - Current

Co-Founder (food blogger)

- Job arrangement with designer through Trello
- Content Writer
- Photoshooting
- Approach with customer, arrange appointment and fb ads

#### **Hikari Marketing**

Penang, MY Co-Founder

Feb. 2019 - Current

- Approach customer for social media services, sales
- Manage social media, boost, create ads
- Photoshooting, Content Writer

• Jobs distribution & Time Management

### Plexus Manufacturing Sdn.bhd

Penang, MY Jan. 2019 – May. 2019

Intern, Program Department

- Arrange shipping, deal with customer
- Basic computer skills, Excel, Words
- Update weekly report, conduct CNY event (decoration, activity, etc)

## Frank Laurent Coffee Roasters/Chick n Waffle

Penang,MY Aug. 2018 – Nov. 2019

Barista

- Stock check, Event Planner (birthday, gathering, etc)
- Basic coffee knowledge
- Customer Service, waitress

## Mark & Spencer

Penang,MY Jun. 2015 – July. 2017

Food, Lingerie, Ladies Sales Advisor

- Stock Take
- Push sales, sales assistance, 1-1 personal service
- Cashier
- Write report every week,
- Basic Computer Skills, Microsoft Words, power point, Excel

## **Popular**

Penang, MY Dec. 2014 – Dec. 2015

English department Assistant

- processing transaction and coordinating book reservations
- stacking bookshelves and fulfill customers need
- Cashier

## **EDUCATION & CREDENTIALS**

Diploma in Accountancy, Finance and Business, 2015-2017

Major: Diploma in Business Administration Tungku Abdul Rahman University College

Cumulative GPA: 3.05

Barchelor of Business (Hons) in Management, 2017-2019

Major: Management Disted College

Cumulative GPA: 3.33

# **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

Photo Editor VSCO · Lightroom · SnapSeed · Phonto

# **PROFESSIONAL AFFILIATIONS & VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE**

Student Representative Council

#### Penang, MY

**Public Relation** 

- Sponsorship
  - Control event flow, Traffic

## Calligraphy Workshop

## Penang, MY

Person In Charge, Host

- 6-8 student per section, in charge of 4 hours workshop individual
- From A to Z
- Interact with student

# Social Responsibility

# Penang, MY

Volunteer

- Volunteered as a performer to performing dance during new year
- Donation of food, clothes